In a dense forest
lived a notorious Lion...
...who hunted all the animals
which came in his sight.
He hunted the animals...
...not only for his meal...
...but for fun too.
So day by day...
...the animal count in the forest
began to drop.
All the animals were worried.
One day, all the animals...
...gathered under a big banyan tree
for a meeting.
Everyday we are losing many animals.
You know it dragged
my uncle yesterday.
Last week it seized my two kids
who were playing outside my house.
My wife too was.
He tied my brother around it's
waist and went away.
If this continues like this...
...in due course none of us would
be alive or exist in this forest.
We need to stop this.
Brother, please why don’t you
suggest an idea to stop this?
I am just thinking on it.
All of them remained silent
for some time.
Listen to me carefully.
Let’s take turns and send
one each from a family.
The Lion will eat where it stays.
As time passes
he would forget to hunt...
...and hence we can live
without worrying...
...when we would be likely killed.
It sounds good.
We should tell this plan to the Lion.
Oh, God!
Who would say this to him?
Hey, brother Fox.
You say this to him, please.
I need to do this too.
Ok, I will do it. But one thing...
...everyone should accompany me
when I meet him.
Next day all the animals
went near the Lion’s cave.
The Lion, on seeing them together,
exclaimed!
Aah...ha! My good time.
It looks as though time is by my side.
Whom do I pick first?
The Fox slowly stepped forward...
...and explained their plan.
The rest were waiting eagerly...
...to hear the Lion’s decision.
Your plan sounds good.
Okay.
I would not kill anybody
but for the one you send.
One thing you should remember.
My prey needs to be in my cave
everyday morning by 10 o’clock.
If not...
From that day, every day...
...one animal went into the
Lion’s cave.
Aah...ha!
What a lovely and luxurious life!
Months rolled on.
It was the turn of a Hare.
The Hare woke up in the morning.
What do I do now?
Today it’s my turn.
For my folk’s sake...
...I need to be the Lion’s prey today.
But still, the Hare...
...somehow wanted to escape
from the Lion’s hand.
Thinking deep...
...the Rabbit moved towards
the cave’s direction.
After crossing some distance...
I feel thirsty. I want water.
Where do I get from?
He looked around in search of water...
...and found a well
in a little distance.
The Hare came close to the well
and peeped inside.
Aah! I have got an idea!
Now I can play the trick
and will handle the Lion.
At the same time...
...the Lion was waiting for his meal.
These animals,
what guts they have!
My prey has not arrived so...
Please! Please help!
Please help! Somebody help!
Who, who?
Who is chasing you?
We five of us
were sake as your prey...
...but while coming,
all of a sudden...
...a lion jumped from a ditch
and started to chase us.
Four of them fell prey
and I just escaped.
What?
Another lion challenging me
in this forest?
I will just finish him right now.
Come with me.
Show me where is he?
The Hare took him to the well.
Uh...
He is there! There!
Down there!
The Lion peeped in to see.
He saw his own shadow.
The Lion thought it
to be another lion.
Who are you?
Who are you...?
How dare he talks back to me?
Come out, if you have the guts.
Come out, if you have the guts...
It's high time I finished him off.
Roaring
he jumped into the well.
Not knowing how to swim...
...the Lion drowned.
On hearing the Lion’s death...
...all the animals
celebrated the occasion.